2026-05-27 - chore: add formatted status for get chatbot and ticket dashboard
2026-05-22 - fix: add re generate signed URL at findAll and fingById knowledge
2026-05-21 - feat: endpoint root for healt checker
2026-05-20 - docs: add documentation for forgot password and reset password function
2026-05-19 - feat: add constraint for update status and respond ticket for admin
2026-05-19 - feat: add search message function for chatbot
2026-05-18 - feat: add forgot password and reset password function
2026-05-15 - docs: update readme
2026-05-14 - fix: fix date of creation for each report to gmt+7
2026-05-14 - docs: add documentation for dashboard repo and service
2026-05-14 - fix: fix date of creation for each report to gmt+7
2026-05-14 - fix: fix bug total feedback undefined for export report
2026-05-14 - fix: fix bug total feedback undefined for export report
2026-05-13 - feat: restore previous improvement
2026-05-13 - feat: restore previous improvement
2026-05-13 - docs: restore previous documentation
2026-05-13 - docs: restore previous documentation
2026-05-13 - feat: improving generate report pdf and excel result
2026-05-13 - Merge branch 'feature-dashboard' into staging
2026-05-13 - docs: adjusting documentation for dashboard repo and service
2026-05-13 - feat: improving generate report pdf and excel result
2026-05-13 - fix: add import dashboard module at app module
2026-05-13 - fix: add import dashboard module at app module
2026-05-13 - feat: add log for dashboard service
2026-05-13 - feat: add log for dashboard service
2026-05-12 - feat: add submit feedback for response chatbot and add dashboard module
2026-05-12 - Merge branch 'feature-dashboard' of https://github.com/Eppy-Team/eppy-be into feature-dashboard
2026-05-12 - docs: add documentation for dashboard module
2026-05-12 - feat: add export stats dashboard function
2026-05-12 - feat: add get dashboard ticket function
2026-05-12 - feat: add get dashboard chatbot function
2026-05-12 - docs: add documentations for submit feedback reponse chatbot
2026-05-12 - feat: add submit feedback for response chatbot
2026-05-12 - chore: add atribut feedback for message table
2026-05-12 - Merge branch 'staging' into feature-chat
2026-05-12 - chore: add atribut feedback for message table
2026-05-07 - feat: adjust from send image url to upload image file for chatbot. also delete column content at knowledge articles and delete 2 langchain table
2026-05-07 - docs: adjust documentation for send message chatbot function
2026-05-07 - feat: adjust from send image url to upload image file for chatbot
2026-05-07 - chore: delete column content at knowledge articles and delete 2 langchain table
2026-05-07 - chore: adjust script for deploy.yml
2026-05-07 - chore: adjust script for deploy.yml
2026-05-07 - chore: finalize migrations and update knowledge_articles
2026-05-07 - chore: finalize migrations and update knowledge_articles
2026-05-06 - feat: add presigner url for s3 file
2026-05-06 - feat: add presigner url for s3 file
2026-05-06 - chore: rename tables to plural and add langchain models
2026-05-06 - chore: rename tables to plural and add langchain models
2026-05-06 - fix: fix error in docker dev
2026-05-06 - fix: add command_timeout at deploy.yml
2026-05-06 - fix: add command_timeout at deploy.yml
2026-05-06 - fix: lowercase the repo name
2026-05-06 - fix: lowercase the repo name
2026-05-06 - fix: move the build image from ec2 to ghcr
2026-05-06 - fix: move the build image from ec2 to ghcr
2026-05-06 - fix: add migrate prisma for automation migrate
2026-05-06 - fix: add migrate prisma for automation migrate
2026-05-06 - feat: add logger for global error exception
2026-05-06 - feat: add logger for global error exception
2026-05-06 - fix: delete duplicate npx prisma generate at dockerfile
2026-05-06 - fix: delete duplicate npx prisma generate at dockerfile
2026-05-06 - fix: optimization docker for server
2026-05-06 - fix: optimization docker for server
2026-05-05 - Merge pull request #3 from Eppy-Team/hotfix
2026-05-05 - fix: adjust docker for faster builds
2026-05-05 - Merge pull request #2 from Eppy-Team/hotfix
2026-05-05 - fix: adjust blok environment into env_file
2026-05-05 - Merge pull request #1 from Eppy-Team/staging
2026-05-05 - feat: log for auth service
2026-05-05 - docs: add documentation for mail service
2026-05-05 - feat: add mail service with aws ses and add notif when ticket has been responded
2026-05-05 - feat: adjust request and response with ai for send chat
2026-05-05 - docs: tidy up documentation
2026-05-05 - feat: add cleanupResources for orphaned process in delete function
2026-05-05 - feat: delete function update knowledge
2026-05-05 - feat: adjusting request and response with ai for create knowledge
2026-05-01 - fix: fix prisma generate in dockerfile
2026-05-01 - feat: cors configuration for frontend
2026-04-30 - fix: delete dummy url db in dockerfile
2026-04-30 - docs: add documentation for tickets module
2026-04-30 - feat: add pagination for find all tickets by admin and user
2026-04-30 - feat: add ticket module for user and admin
2026-04-23 - feat: add module chat for chatbot
2026-04-23 - docs: add documentation for each auth module
2026-04-23 - docs: add documentation for each ai module
2026-04-22 - Merge branch 'feature-knowledge' into staging
2026-04-22 - docs: adjust documenatation for each function and class in knowledge module
2026-04-22 - docs: add documentation for each function and class in conversation module
2026-04-22 - feat: add conversation module
2026-04-22 - docs: add comment for documentation at each function and class knowledge
2026-04-22 - feat: adjust update knowledge for not changing embed status
2026-04-22 - refactor: adjusting message and http code at each knowledge endpoint
2026-04-22 - feat: add pagination for get all knowledge
2026-04-22 - refactor: rewrite api response at get detail knowledge
2026-04-22 - feat: add knowledge module and storage module
2026-04-21 - feat(ai): adding service for integration ai. including chat, embed, and check health
2026-04-21 - feat(db): adjusting knowledge_articles table for uploading file
2026-04-17 - feat: ci/cd with github
2026-04-17 - fix: fixing versioning for APIs
2026-04-17 - feat: adding versioning for APIs
2026-04-16 - fix(docker): fixing error at production
2026-04-16 - fix(docker): fixing error at production
2026-04-16 - feat(docker): adding multi stage for production
2026-04-16 - feat: docker initiation
2026-04-11 - feat(auth): adding function to get profile user and refactore response message
2026-04-11 - feat(auth): create function to login and register for auth module
2026-04-09 - feat: setup prisma module, decorators, filters, guards, interceptors, and utils
2026-04-09 - feat: prisma and jwt setup
2026-04-09 - feat:project initiation
